let questions = [
    {   // QUESTION #1
        question: "Who took command of British Forces in North America directly after Thomas Gage?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Lord North",
        choiceB: "William Howe",
        choiceC: "Richard Howe",
        choiceD: "Benjamin Lincoln",
        correct: "B"
    }, { // QUESTION #2
        question: "Where did most of the fighting of Bunker Hill actually take place?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Bunker Hill",
        choiceB: "Nob Hill",
        choiceC: "Hank's Hill",
        choiceD: "Breed's Hill",
        correct: "D"
    },
    {   // QUESTION #3
        question: "How many attempts did it take for the British to take Breed's Hill?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "1",
        choiceB: "2",
        choiceC: "3",
        choiceD: "4",
        correct: "C"
    }, { // QUESTION #4
        question: "Which side suffered greater casualties in the battle of Bunker Hill?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "British",
        choiceB: "American",
        choiceC: "Even",
        choiceD: "French",
        correct: "A"
    }, { // QUESTION #5
        question: "Who's quote is this? 'I wish we could sell them another hill at the same price'",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Nathanael Greene",
        choiceB: "George Washington",
        choiceC: "Israel Putnam",
        choiceD: "George III",
        correct: "A"
    }, { // QUESTION #6
        question: "Which British controlled fort did Benedict Arnold and Ethan Allen take?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Fort Knox",
        choiceB: "Fort McHenry ",
        choiceC: "Fort Sumter ",
        choiceD: "Fort Ticonderoga",
        correct: "D"
    }, { // QUESTION #7
        question: "Which lake is Fort Ticonderoga nearest?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Lake Erie",
        choiceB: "Lake Champlain",
        choiceC: "Lake Ticonderoga ",
        choiceD: "Lake Mead",
        correct: "B"
    }, { // QUESTION #8
        question: "In the Quebec campaign, who was the British general in charge in Canada?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Michael Bolton",
        choiceB: "Banastre Tarleton",
        choiceC: "Guy Carleton",
        choiceD: "Charles Stanton",
        correct: "C"
    }, { // QUESTION #9
        question: "Which American general attacked and occupied Montreal?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Richard Montgomery",
        choiceB: "Henry Knox",
        choiceC: "Nathanael Greene",
        choiceD: "Friedrich Wilhelm von Steuben",
        correct: "A"
    }, { // QUESTION #10
        question: "What injury did Benedict Arnold recieve in the Quebec campaign?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Amputated feet from frostbite",
        choiceB: "Stabbed in left eye",
        choiceC: "Hanged to death",
        choiceD: "Shot in the leg",
        correct: "D"
    }
];